# PHATTHARANIT PEWKLIENG

# WEB DEVELOPER

New Zealand Citizenship

#### CONTACT

021 02530921

phattharanit.noei@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/phattharanit -pewklieng-845752122/



#### **EXPERTISE**

As a recent Dev graduate, I have honed my skills in JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Testing, and RESTful APIs.
Additionally, I bring management experience from my time as a Store Manager, where I developed expertise in technical support, hardware, and software. With excellent communication and customer service skills, I actively participate in coding and group projects, applying agile methodologies and problem-solving skills. I have also developed proficiency in CSS frameworks, including Tailwind CSS, to create visually appealing and responsive websites.

My strengths include exceptional customer service, strong problem-solving abilities, and the ability to work under pressure, coupled with highly organized planning and scheduling. I am motivated in team environments and independent work, with a talent for adaptability and creativity. Lastly, I have experience in employee and peer-to-peer training.

# LANGUAGES

English, Thai

#### AWARDS

Partner of Period 2022

# REFERENCES

Available on request.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Trainee - Full Stack Web Developer**

Dev Academy Aotearoa

Jan 2023 - May 2023

- Completed 17-week web development training, including 5 weeks of selfdirected study and a 9-week hands-on coding bootcamp in a real-life working environment.
- Collaborated in programming pairs and teams to tackle coding challenges and group projects.
- · Applied agile methodologies resulting in functioning applications.
- Worked on a web app for restaurants that simplified the ordering process, allowing customers to order through a unique QR code that sent orders directly to the kitchen. Owners and administrators could manage the menu and monitor all orders through the app.
- Developed a personalised food recipe project that suggests dishes to users based on available ingredients, streamlining the cooking process and providing creative meal ideas.

# **Store Manager**

Starbucks, St Lukes

Jun 2020 - Feb 2023

- Recruited, interviewed, and managed team members, processed staff payroll, and conducted regular performance reviews to ensure everything was up to standard.
- Led by example, provided effective training, and motivated team members to consistently achieve store targets, KPIs, and improve operational efficiency.
- Analyzed sales figures, forecasted future sales volumes, and managed inventory accordingly.
- Created weekly schedules based on sales trends and events to optimize labor utilization.

#### **Shift Supervisor**

Starbucks, 220 Queen Street

Jun 2017 - Jun 2020

- Provided exceptional customer service and resolved customer complaints promptly
- Trained staff on company standards for product merchandising, line display, stocking, storing of products, and distribution of marketing material
- · Handled cash, verified safe, and made daily deposits

#### KitchenHand & Waitress

Thai Village Restaurant, Remuera

Feb 2012 - Jun 2017

- Provided front-line customer service
- Performed kitchen hand duties, waitressing, and taking orders and requests
- Operated cash registers handling cash and processing electronic payments
- Conducted cleaning and general housekeeping

#### Education

Dev Academy Aotearoa, Auckland Jan 2023 - May 2023

Certificate in Applied Software Development

Auckland University of Technology, Auckland Jul 2016 - Nov 2016

Postgraduate Certificate in Computer and Information

Sciences

Unitec Institute of Technology, Auckland Feb 2012 - Nov 2015
Bachelor of Computing Systems